Kontakt

sebastianpost@online.de

www.linkedin.com/in/sebastianpost-601356243 (LinkedIn) sebastianpost96.github.io/ personal-website/ (Personal)

Top-Kenntnisse

Distributed Systems
Full-Stack Development
TypeScript

Languages

English (Full Professional)
German (Native or Bilingual)

Sebastian Post

Frontend Developer at nerdware GmbH

Schweinfurt, Bayern, Deutschland

Zusammenfassung

Experienced frontend developer with a specialization in Angular, reactive programming and enterprise application state management. Strong project background in ERP and HRM systems, along with contributions to public libraries. Committed to continuous professional growth in software development.

Berufserfahrung

nerdware GmbH Frontend Developer Oktober 2022 - Present (8 Monate)

Working on multinational HR support system.

AraCom IT Services AG
Frontend Developer
April 2021 - September 2022 (1 Jahr 6 Monate)
Bamberg, Bayern, Deutschland

Projects on Enterprise Resource Planning and Internationalization.

Ronny T-Shirt Druck IT Administrator (Minijob) 2015 - 2021 (6 Jahre) Bamberg, Bavaria, Germany

- Onlineshop web development
- SEO
- Maintenance of soft- and hardware

Ausbildung

Otto-Friedrich-Universität Bamberg
Bachelor of Science - BS, Software Systems Science · (Oktober 2017 - März 2021)